Quiz_data = [

{
    "question": "What time is displayed?",
    "choices": ["A. 5:30", "B. 7:00", "C. 12:15", "D. 8:45"],
    "answer": "B. 7:00"
},
    
{
    "question": "What time is displayed?",
    "choices": ["A. 6:45", "B. 4:50", "C. 9:00", "D. 12:20"],
    "answer": "D. 12:20"
},
    
{
    "question": "What time is displayed?",
    "choices": ["A. 7:30", "B. 11:55", "C. 2:10", "D. 1:25"],
    "answer": "C. 2:10"
},
    
{
    "question": "What time is displayed?",
    "choices": ["A. 3:00", "B. 10:25", "C. 5:05", "D. 7:35"],
    "answer": "A. 3:00"
},

{
    "question": "What time is displayed?",
    "choices": ["A. 8:15", "B. 12:45", "C. 9:10", "D. 4:00"],
    "answer": "B. 12:45"
},

{
    "question": "What time is displayed?",
    "choices": ["A. 7:30", "B. 11:55", "C. 2:10", "D. 1:25"],
    "answer": "D. 1:25"
},

{
    "question": "What time is displayed?",
    "choices": ["A. 5:30", "B. 7:00", "C. 12:15", "D. 8:45"],
    "answer": "C. 12:15"
},

{
    "question": "What time is displayed?",
    "choices": ["A. 7:00", "B. 11:20", "C. 2:10", "D. 1:25"],
    "answer": "B. 11:20"
},

{
    "question": "What time is displayed?",
    "choices": ["A. 6:45", "B. 4:00", "C. 10:30", "D. 12:20"],
    "answer": "A. 6:45"
},

{
    "question": "What time is displayed?",
    "choices": ["A. 4:50", "B. 10:25", "C. 5:40", "D. 7:35"],
    "answer": "D. 7:35"
},

]